LLMs are really good at writing crappy
software on demand for basically free.
So like it's not good software often if
unless you have the right structures and
approaches and the right kind of
scaffolding to make sure that it's doing
the thing that you wanted like what you
all are building and that these
radically change how we think of where
you would apply software and how you
would apply it.
You're listening to the AI native dev
brought to you by Tesla.
[Music]
Hello, Simon Maple here and welcome to
another episode of the AI Native Dev. We
have a special one for you this time
around as we reshare an AI native Devcon
session. The one where Dion has a chat
with Alex Kamaroski about the AI
developer ecosystem. Now, one of the
reasons why we want to share this
session is because we actually have a
new AI Native DevCon event fast
approaching on May 13th, 2025. It's our
spring edition. So, yeah, we'll be also
having a full edition later in November
2025. At the time of recording, the CFP,
the call for papers, and the
registration are both open. So, head to
a native.io/events
io/events where you can submit your
proposals to speak at the event as well
as of course snag your ticket and your
spot for the event as well. It's free to
join us. So with that, be sure to
subscribe and like the video if you're
watching it on YouTube. And I'll hand
over to Dion and Alex. Hey, how's it
going, Alex? Good. How are you? Thanks
for having me. Yeah, pretty good. Thanks
so much for for joining us. Uh you're a
little early your time. Whereabouts are
you? I am in Berkeley. Oh, very nice.
That's good. That's good. So, yeah. How
did Bits and Bobs come about? Actually,
was I right in that? Yeah, it's So, I
have this the compendium, which is that
sort of custom web app I built over the
last number of years to organize my
thoughts. And if you look at the
compendium live, you'll think that it's
dead. I haven't added anything to it for
years. I actually add have it open every
day and I have I add hundreds of notes
to it every day in my private working
notes area. I use embeddings to help me
find commonalities across different
ideas. And then each week I go and spend
a few hours on the weekends when the
kids are napping and I distill out the
notes from that week that resonate with
me and I develop them a little bit. And
it started off actually as a believe it
or not as a practice a very early
version of it was when I used to report
to Clay Bour who recently founded that
Sierra with Brett Taylor. I would send a
email on Monday to him of here's the
people I'm meeting with here's the
things that I'm doing and here's a few
takeaways like interesting ideas I think
you might find relevant. And then I
continued that practice at Stripe and
then I kind of that section got deeper
and deeper and longer and longer and I
started sharing it with more and more
people in my internal little strategy
study groups and then into internal
blogs and then I started publishing
externally because I do I do all that
reflection on my own personal time and
yeah now it's a document that has a
stupid number of pages in it and the
it's really slow. One of the things that
happens is people when they're searching
in it, it takes so long to load that
they're searching and it will Google
Docs will think that they're typing into
the document and so it suggests a random
edit to the document because they're
actually just searching for something in
the document. So it happens like once a
day. I think I'm probably going to split
it's I think 700 pages or something and
again I add like 20 pages or so a week
which is just silly. I know it's
probably one of their stress test. So,
we're going to get into talking about
the future, but curious actually to
start with the past a little bit like
with this round of, you know, AI uh and
you know, kind of Gen AI, when did this
first hit home for you? Were you super
skeptical at first? And was there a bit
of an aha moment that got you thinking
like maybe there's something real here?
Yeah, I've been following obviously all
the papers and interesting developments
at Google research and others for many
years and watching it slowly plot along
and some of the silly things that people
were doing with the earlier versions of
chat bots. And the moment that really
hit home for me though is I have a few
groups of people I facilitate of
interesting thinkers I just like talking
to and having collaborative debate with.
And once a year or so, we would get an
Airbnb in the woods and we would go and
we just have a few days like 12 people
just for an interesting long-term
discussion about what's going to happen
in the next decade about crypto and not
just for crypto but for all of society.
And then the next year we did generative
AI and that was I think a few weeks
before chatbt came out and we had a
number of folks good friends people who
you know as well in the session is just
like three days of just thinking and
pulling on threads and afterwards I
would sit down and I would just write 60
pages of here's what I took away from
that discussion and I remember writing
down and be like holy like this is
going to change everything and it's on
the cusp of it's it so many things
change that people haven't even realized
yet and and then a Few weeks later,
chatbt comes out and it was like just
like you know starting bell for
everybody and I knew at that point that
like this was going to be like LLMs are
not some flash in the pan. They are not
some random technology like they are a
fundamental disruptive innovation and I
think you need to act like it. I think a
lot of people are acting like AI is a
sustaining innovation and I don't think
that's true at all. I think it radically
changes a number of things that we
haven't even we're like wy coyote out
over the cliff as a as an industry.
We're like, "Oh, we're just going to
slap some AI on this." That's how that
works at all. Actually changes
fundamentally the way that we write
software, the way that we can we can
experience things and it changes the
cost structures of everything. It's a
really interesting and fascinating
thing. But it was that Yeah, it was that
period right before Chat DVD came out
that I was like, "Oh, wow." Got it.
That's awesome. So, this event is called
AI Native Dev and I'm It's can be a
little bit of a double on tandra, can
mean different things. I'm curious what
that means for you. I think people are
currently attempting, they're just
jamming AI on the sides of the way that
they built software before and the way
that they would approach problems. And I
think when you embrace LLMs, you write
software differently and you think of
it, it's almost like how do you pull the
software out of the mind of this LLM?
And you do it in a way that's not
traditional collaborating with another
person. you do it a lot more like what
Tesla's doing, I think, of like specs
and this designing a thing. Like I had a
silly little example. There's this game
called Sky Joe. That's a fun little card
game. And we were playing it and I got
really into it. I realized, oh, if you
could count the cards going through, you
would have a better you could
strategically be making better calls.
And so I wanted to make a little web app
to make it so you could just keep track
of the cards that had been played out of
the deck and it would tell you the
probabilities of different cards coming
up or whatever. This is the kind of
thing that would have taken me a few
hours on a weekend. Sit down, create a
new project from scratch and like slowly
add in stuff. And what I did instead was
I built it in 10 minutes and I just used
anthropic artifacts and I did it exactly
the way I would have done it. I said
first write a little function that does
this. Okay, now put that function in
this. Now add TypeScript typing that
allows like now like I just told it what
I would have done for each of the
individual steps. And in 10 minutes, you
have this really nice, nicely styled
thing that has undo and save and all
these little features. And I built it
like not by writing any code, but by
just coaxing it in the right order with
the right steps and things I wanted to
do. And that was that felt like a
radically different way of building
software to me than sitting down and
writing this little hobby project that
would have taken me a few hours to do.
Yeah. Do you think that that kind of app
like this notion of a I think some
people like micro apps and the like is
going to change the way that a bunch of
even like users and non-developers maybe
even getting into this world where they
can scratch their own itches where like
at the moment maybe they just like I
could do spreadsheets so I try and use a
spreadsheet to do everything that I can
like they have these different tools but
they don't feel like they can create
custom software. I think it will but for
a couple reasons. So I was a friend of
mine is not particularly technical and
they knew I was super into playing
around with AI and they said I want to
see what it can do. I wanted to have it
programmed. So we went to chat GBT and
they were saying a thing they wanted to
do and then they give the HTML and I
copy and paste it into a thing and then
load it into separate tab and that step
mystified him. I don't understand what's
happening and the feedback loop just
took enough time to like copy paste and
then sometimes it would tell you you
have to like surgically put it back in
the code back into the because it would
only update a small portion of it. And
then we switched to anthropic. It has
artifacts. And that was basically the
same loop just in a live preview. And
that radically changed it. Instead of it
feeling of me handholding him, he just
sat there and was doing little things
and experimenting with it. And I left. I
came back 20 minutes later and he built
a relatively complex little toy app. And
he was like, I guess I'm a programmer
now. I was like, yeah, sure. But it felt
like this immediiacy, I think, felt
really nice. I think by default what
we'll see with AI and the current
distribution physics is we'll see a
proliferation of both hyper centralized
hyperagregators and profusion of lots of
little micro apps that are like little
toys that they don't really do that much
on their own. I think the real trick
will be how can you get figure out a
system that allows these micro apps to
add up to something much larger than
some of their parts to interact with
other micro apps and other experiences
and have this emergent possibility
that's quite challenging and I think
that requires a like a fundamentally
different kind of like substrate to be
built on and that's one of the things
that we're working on. So much of
software, so much of the industry is
predicated to the idea that software is
expensive to write and cheap to run. And
LM's mess with both of these assumptions
because code that uses LMS to execute,
which is not all code in the future, but
a fair bit of it, that now has a
marginal cost that is above zero, which
means it is expensive in some
significant way that we're not used to.
And secondarily, LM are really good at
writing crappy software on demand for
basically free. So it's not good
software often if unless you have the
right structures and approaches and the
right kind of scaffolding to make sure
that it's doing the thing that you
wanted like what you all were building
but it is a and that these radically
change how we think of where you would
apply software and how you would apply
it. Clay Shark has this old essay from I
think it's 2007 called situated software
and it's now off the internet yet has a
mirror of it. It's a great essay and it
talks about situated software as
software that is situated to a
hyperspecific context. So, anytime
you've written a spreadsheet formula,
that's situated software, it's situated
specifically in the context of this
particular spreadsheet. And anytime that
someone looks at someone else's bit of
situated software, they go, "That's
piece of crap. It barely works. It's
insecure. It's ugly." But to the person
who built it, it's perfect. It does
exactly and precisely what they need.
And sometimes in those contexts,
actually, what happens that breaks? You
said, "I don't know. I'll just slap some
more situated software on the side." And
especially when LM can help you write
the situated software, you can get
software that's just right. It's just
the right size for you as opposed to
this oneizefits- none software that we
have today in our modern era. Yeah, that
makes sense. Some people I see snarky
about I can just do these little toy
things, right? You stay in your zone.
Stay in the micro apps era. I'm an
amazing expert developer and you're
never going to be able to touch me and
the domain that I understand and my
enterprise software and the like. How do
you think over time especially like LLMs
are actually going to be able to help
you know in very broad ways across of
the spectrum of development that's out
there or do you think it will never Oh
no it for sure and I think folks like
Tesla and others are really pushing the
limits of what you can get. I think the
big story by the way the last year
people talk about the quality
improvements to me it's the context
length improvements that just radically
changes the kinds of questions you could
ask if you wanted to ask before of a
large book what are the major themes of
this book you can't answer it with rag
it's not possible because it's not like
there's a like this is the theme and
that's in the embedding like you have to
have a broad context and the more that
you have this broad context the more
that you can see these subtle patterns
keep track of and understand where
things are going and so I feel like
we're just at the beginning stages of
figuring ing out how to get LLM to build
large bits of software. I also think one
of the things that's excited about
Tesla's approach is LLM one of their
superpowers is they're really good at
translation and you can translate
English to code. And so before like the
spec is not just some little
documentation. It actually is almost the
primary semantic thing and the actual
code is I think like compiling the spec
into code and it's unlike a normal
compiler where everyone who's learned C
at the beginning certain point says the
compiler's broken. I can guarantee you
this compiler is not broken for for this
case. So you learn that the compiler is
almost always trustworthy. With LLMs
like it can get confused and the thing
that gets confused on most is when it's
not it's not high locality of the code
when it's in multiple files. It has to
coordinate based on a specific phrase or
word that has to be consistent in these
multiple places. LMS tend to kind of get
a little bit confused by that kind of
situation. But there's ways of adding
scaffolding and idioms to make it so
they are more likely to stay to a pretty
good answer. Yeah. I think one of my
realizations around this was feeling
like I was using English to poke at
things just like you were talking about.
But then all of that information was
lost. It was like in the chat session
and it was gone. And it was like but
that was like my actual record like
Yeah. recording the steps of things to
get to the that result. Yeah. So it felt
like I'm compiling this thing and then
just taking my compiled output with me.
Yeah. Wait a minute. Isn't the other
thing the important thing to stay
around? So what if that could be the
canonical piece instead? And and so
that's why specs made a lot of sense to
me. As you've poked around with all
these things, what have you found,
you've mentioned some of these like LLMs
to be particularly good at or bad at
when it comes to coding and development
in general? One way to think about this
is Jurassic Park when they have they
have gaps in the dinosaur DNA and it
fills it in with frog DNA kind of LLMs
do that too where if you don't bring the
specific examples it just assumes based
on the most generic background
information of how it fits in. So they
do really well if you're writing it in
the same kind of React style that
everybody else writes it. They're really
good at that because they've got tons of
frog DNA to bring into your particular
situation to get really good results. If
you're writing an algorithm that's been
represented is like nicely cleanly
separated and exists in lots of
tutorials and Wikipedia articles or
whatever, they're also pretty good at
reproducing that. When you have an
architecture like a relatively large
architecture that is slightly atypical
or has some weird stylistic and calling
ways it's been designed, architected,
they start getting a little bit funky
there and a little bit like they can
lose the plot a bit. remember that like
LLMs can't count and the it's miracle in
some ways that they work reasonably that
they can handle some of these cases. One
of the reasons like really deeply nested
JSON they lose track of am I in an
object context or an array context and
they'll like mis nest some of the things
partially because it's just really hard
to keep track of the counting. One way
looking at this is they do a really good
job of these seen objects like that. the
smaller chunks of JSON that are shaped
roughly like that just in way more
examples because presumably the JSON
you'd see on the web has a logarithmic
kind of fall-off of like the larger
sizes get increasingly less less common
and so it doesn't have as much training
data to keep track of and it can't
fundamentally count and so it just kind
of loses track of and just it's remember
it's all like vibes based programming
it's just its vibes are extremely dialed
in yeah and it's fascinating because
like you mentioned there's a lot of
React code on the internet that has
ended up in these models and the like.
And then I start to think about the frog
DNA. It's do we have the kind of meh
frog because most of the DNA that's
gotten in there with React code is from
the average React developer, not like
the React core developer that's out
there. And so is there like that magical
piece of like actually the shark DNA
that hasn't evolved that much? Right.
It's like it's just gotten really good
and honed in. And so you really want
something that's good enough that that's
got enough content that's out there but
is also really focused. I'm really
curious about the notion of also just
like kingmaking as well. If we created a
brand new language today, do we have a
chance to make it? And how do you feel?
How do you think about the role of data
and quality data and golden path data,
all of those things with LLMs? I love
the shark data. I just writing that
down. The Yeah, LM are really good at
imitation. They're so insanely good at
imitation that it sometimes looks like
innovation, but they're really
fundamentally kind of conceptually
interpolating across just a very wide
swath of human experience and examples.
And that does feel like it pulls us
towards the centroidid. It pulls us
towards the average mushy center. like
when you in it's writing it default
writing style is like corporate speak
because that's the mushy center that at
the core like the the random bland heat
death average kind of and we get the
same thing in programming where I just
kind use react and we have to just do it
whatever the most basic way you can
possibly like basic in the pjorative
sense and I do think it it one thing
that's interesting and challenging like
one of the ways that it knows how to
weight what things are good is like
things that have worked for others in
the past are more likely to be
replicated and other people to also talk
about them and write about them. And so
Labs aren't random sampling all text
that could exist. They're random
sampling the text that humans have found
useful enough to propagate, right? And
you have this natural thing where humans
are selecting to some degree the thing
that it's reading off of. And but over
time as more and more that selection is
done from like this disbasian kind of
averaging process, you lose some of that
signal. And it does feel like it will
pull us more towards the centroidid. It
also does feel like to me it'll be much
harder to escape local maxima because
it's just in default if I don't have a
strong opinion about how to write this
bit of code and I said do a thing that
has this behavior what's it going to
reach for? It's going to reach for the
most obvious basic answer of that and
put it in there and I don't have a
strong opinion so I'm not going to go
through. No, no, no, no. Do it in this
other style that I think is interesting.
And so that's fine. And so now you'll
have yet another piece that is now put
onto the whole collection of of Yeah,
that's funny. Now I'm thinking about how
to nudge selection to be like this
software passes tests a lot versus what
are the other parts of selection that
could help nudge things fast. So I've
noticed in the past you've mentioned
that spending time to define
requirements saves extraordinary amounts
of time and so I'm just curious what
does requirement just like when we talk
about specs it means lots of different
things to different people like what do
you mean by that? Uh I think it's part
partially that one was my direct
experience in the last few weeks and
I've realized it's a pattern I've seen
many many times like oh we understand
how to build this I've got the idea in
my head we will simply execute this it
turns out explaining the requirements
like you have like this hyperobject in
your head of this should work and all
the pieces and if it's like this and
explaining to other people is like
serialization process it takes so long
and it's like cominatorial kind of thing
to really serialize it perfectly and the
way to communicate it is then factor
that serialization into higher level
requirements, which is a process that
takes a ton of time. And so you're
always like, "Oh, we're fine. We're
fine. We're just gonna we're just going
to wing it. I'm just going to give
enough guidance or whatever." But if you
do this improperly, you're like, "Oh, we
go fast by not doing the requirements or
factoring out the worker requirements."
And then what you end up with is you
realize later that people didn't
understand the fundamental thing you
were trying to do and they went in these
other weird corners and you have to
like, "No, no, actually there's a whole
thing. You can't do it that way. You
gotta do it this way." And they go,
"Okay, cool. I had to throw out this
entire thing I just did now." now and so
to them it feels like a total thrash and
the mental model in my head is like a
dynamic programming problem without
memorization done in exactly the wrong
order. So each calculation you're doing
20 time 30 30 times or whatever and
that's what it feels like it to do the
requirements like to me the requirements
process is taking the serialization of
the hyperobject and then distilling it
into a more abstract and condensed
version that can be efficiently
communicated to somebody else. Yeah,
that makes sense. Some developers
initially got excited about having these
new tools. Some developers got a little
bit nervous at first of is AI going to
take my job and that whole meme. When
you look ahead 5 10 years out there like
what aspects do you think of software
development are going to remain
fundamentally human driven and what
parts do you think we're going to be
somewhat happy to pass over to be
AIdriven? Yeah, I think that I'm
personally excited about AI as a tool
for human creativity because it takes
the the bland drudgery and allows you to
handle those parts, the parts that
aren't exciting or aren't interesting,
aren't surprising to you in any way,
just allows you to execute on those way
faster. And one of the powers of
infrastructure in general, one of the
reasons infrastructure works and creates
value in the world is instead of every
single individual customer having to
build their own lower layers, you can
build it once and share it across many.
You write it once, you share it with
many. So everybody's getting that value,
but the cost is a single instance of it.
So you're factoring out the most boring
parts of people, a lots of people's
jobs. LLMs also factor out the most
boring parts, the parts that are just
the mundane judgery. And I think that if
you use them properly and see them as a
tool to extend your creativity, they
allow you to do other interesting new
things. Like I've heard a number of
people have told me they've started
writing poetry and they're like, "Yeah,
I just I used to like it in like high
school. I haven't done it in a while and
now I've got like a brainstorming
writing partner that helps me come up
with a better rhyme for that or eight
different examples of this or critique
the thing with that because like if I
show the poetry even to my spouse I
don't want to show them like a shitty
writer and so I think it's those kinds
of things that allow people to stretch
further and I think it's an act of
choice. It is also just as easy to take
those tools and become increasingly
passive and increasingly like cool now I
have to think very hard. I think you
should use these tools to help you think
harder. Yeah, that makes sense. So, we
both spent a lot of our careers working
on the web platform as we mentioned at
the beginning and I think we both had a
love towards the kind of openness of
that era and then we got to see mobile
which guy had mentioned this GIO
mentioned this in the keynote was
slightly different shape of of openness
which had different effects. So someone
who like really studies ecosystem
dynamics and the like, how do you think
AI is going to potentially change the
landscape as it comes to what can happen
to the existing ecosystems like how's
this going to affect the web and mobile
and what opportunities it maybe give us
in the future to to have change. Yeah, I
think that t typically the like
decentralization centralization is like
a tick tock. It's at the beginning stage
of a new disruptive paradigm. It's open
and decentralized and then later it
centralizes as the best patterns are
found and become like the compounding
advantage to the ones who are best at it
gets stronger and stronger and you get
to a really boring part with that
because there's just everything
interesting has been done like there's
no space for innovation. It's just I
don't know if one of these three big
players think that it's allowed to exist
and it's allowed to exist. That's insane
to me. And so I think my that's one of
my hopes of AI as a disruptive
innovation is that it resets and gives
you into this openended decentralized
world to start again. I think in some
ways AI there was a real danger a number
like a year and a half ago I thought
that AI would be an inherently
centralizing technology. It's so capital
intensive that like only a very small
number of companies can possibly invest
the capital and then now they become the
only ones that can train and host these
large models. And that was a very real
possibility. Like I think looking at a
year and a half ago, there was a really
real possibility that OpenAI would just
be the hyper aggregator, the apex
aggregator to rule them all in this new
world and we jump straight from
centralized to hyper centralized and
like that would be it. And I think very
encouragingly for society one anthropic
built a better model. Sonet 3.5 is my
daily driver. I use it every day. I use
it all the time. It's like arguably a
better model on a number of fronts which
means now there's another at least
there's multiple horses in the race.
Gemini has been making a lot of really
interesting progress and then Zuckerberg
comes along and Madi just goes, "Hey,
here's an open weights model that is
actually one of the best in class which
really scramles all the dynamics in a
really healthy way." I think happens now
is instead of the AI model producers
having this extreme centralizing force,
they look a lot more like to me like
cell network providers of extremely
capital intensive and also not that much
pricing power because they're basically
commodities and you have lots of
different options to pick from which is
I think really beneficial for society
because those individual operators don't
have that much strategic power but all
of us benefit from there being a nice
competition and allows an open ecosystem
to thrive on top of that. One of the
bets I was asserting a year ago is
companies that take AI for granted can
do some really interesting things. If
you are fighting to build frontier
models that compete with the big ones,
wow, that is a really tough space to be
in. But if you say, I'm just going to
assume that there's going to be good
competition and there will be multiple
good cheap options to pick from. That
competition will drive the quality up
and the cost down consistently. That's a
pretty safe assumption. I don't care who
wins. I don't care which ones of these
or whoever. I just know that there will
be good high-quality cheap models to use
and that seems like a pretty safe
assumption at this point which allows an
open ecosystem on top which I think is
enormously exciting for society. Yeah,
that makes sense. And then another thing
that I love about the web ecosystem is
browser extensions of all things like it
felt like you've got this aftermarket
kind of approach where I can come along
and someone can build a thing that
changes the thing for me. And do you
think AI ecosystems are going to allow
for maybe a more personal custom
experiences that I can maybe experience
the Streamyard system that I'm in now
with a few different tweaks without
having to persuade that company to make
that change for me which obviously
doesn't scale. I think so. And I think I
think back to Gree Monkey. I think Gree
Monkey was one of the golden eras of the
browser of these little scripts that you
could put in. And one of my good friends
is used to run users scripts.org which
was the kind of centralized community
for that. And I think grease monkey is
really powerful. The problem with grease
monkey ultimately was it was insecure
and fundamentally so even as a savvy
user choosing a set of scripts to put in
your thing. There's like a there's a
curve that looks like this. Like I will
only install 10 of these because I have
to really trust that they aren't going
to mess with my Gmail or sell my data or
whatever. And I think the trick is how
can you get that kind of thing and I
would never tell my dad to install it.
My god, can you imagine what terrible
crazy stuff you would have installed and
would run in grease monkey? So, how do
you change the security and privacy
model to make it so that actually it's
just a purely yep, keep on going and the
sky's is the limit and everybody should
be able to tweak. I think that's
possible, but requires a thinking about
the security and privacy models. It
can't just be like duct taped on to the
existing privacy models. Got it. Makes
sense. Okay. I noticed there's some
questions that have been asked here, so
I want to get to them so I don't take
all of your time. Min asked, "How does a
developer new to creating a micro app
ensure that the code created created is
of good quality and safe? Are there
known techniques to use when interacting
with an LLM?" This is one of the things
that is why micro apps are useful in
this context. If you certain code that's
compiled, if it compiles, there's a
pretty good chance it at least does
something correct. And this is like a is
also, by the way, is a nice loop for
LLMs of if it doesn't compile, you tell
it back to the LLM, here's the code you
gave me. Here's the compile error. fix
it and it can do a pretty good job.
That's like kind of automated spoke
testing. The problem is like the
semantics to get the semantics of the
thing correct. And one of the nice
things about little micro apps and one
of the reasons they're a sweet spot is
because you can just poke at it and you
poke the five buttons in the right
order. Does it do the thing I expected?
There's not too many like the comtorial
space of possibility isn't that large,
but you have to go to interact with it
and poke at it and go, "Yeah, it does
the thing I wanted." Or, "Nope, wait a
second. It I hit this button and it did
the thing that's wrong. Try again, LM."
But like the bigger it gets, the more
likely that you've gotten something that
has gotten something wrong. And that's
where the importance of testing becomes
extraordinarily important. And I think
one of the reasons that what you all are
doing is really interesting is if you
write the spec, it's also easy to write
the tests. And I find that like the
biggest reason people don't write tests
in practice because it's really it's
such a log and it's such a pain in the
butt and you're it's you're doing it in
a way that feels very different than
writing the code. to it that only
attacks but is the thing that allows you
to go fast later. MS also are honestly
they don't get bored totally willing to
write the boring annoying test and maybe
it's not exactly correct but it's more
likely to catch a thing that is wrong in
the future and like maybe you dive into
go oh this test was wrong but that's the
thing that gives you that smoke the
smoke test that helps you know that I
should dive in and try to debug. Yeah.
Okay. Anthony asked, "What are the best
examples you've seen of stringing
together micro apps or their functions?
Incumbents today like Zapia for
workflows comes to mind." I think we are
not even in the first inning of this. I
feel like so far we're seeing really
interesting stuff like GitHub Spark is
interesting and obviously anthropic
artifacts was interesting and what is
doing with Vzero is super interesting
but these are all individual micro apps.
they aren't even distributable
necessarily like that for anthropic like
it's almost an afterthought that you can
distribute the artifact and others you
can't and so I don't think we we know
what good looks like in this yet I think
that there's a because we haven't even
started we we as a as an ecosystem has
discovered that micro apps are a sweet
spot for LLMs but we haven't yet figured
out like what to do with that okay in a
world of lots of micro apps how do you
stitch them together I think that's an
open question that we're still no one
has really gotten a good handle on yet
yeah awesome but Alex, thanks so much
for taking the time. I could talk to you
for hours about this stuff. It's been
really fun and yeah, find find Alex
online. Can't wait to hear more about
your startup. It's called Common Tools.
Is that right? Y yeah, super excited
about that. And yeah, join the Discord
and ask questions there, too. And we'll
be looking over it. But Alex, thanks so
much. Of course. Great seeing you.
Thanks for having me. Cheers. A big
thank you there to Dion and Alex. And a
reminder that the call for papers for
the AI Native DevCon spring edition
that's happening on May 13th is still
open at the time of recording as well as
registrations. So head to a
native.io/events where you can submit
your proposals to speak for the event as
well as snag your tickets for the event
as well for free. So, thanks for
listening to the episode of the Native
Dev and be sure to subscribe as well as
hit that thumbs up if you're on YouTube
and tune in to the next episode. Bye for
now. Thanks for tuning in. Join us next
time on the AI Native Dev brought to you
by Tesla.
[Music]